Attached you will find a 100011-word excerpt from the novel 揂 Tale of Two Cities?by Charles Dickens (A_tale_of_two_cities.100kwords.original.txt).
You will also find an obfuscated version where each instance of the words 揳?and 搕he?have been replaced by the words 揳?or 搕he?(A_tale_of_two_cities.100kwords.obfuscated.txt).
牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋牋?

Your task is to resolve the 揳/the?ambiguity in the latter version as best as possible via a computer program. Note this program should not access any part of the novel 揂 Tale of Two Cities?to accomplish this; i.e. it cannot 搕rain on?or 搈emorize?this particular novel. 燳ou are otherwise free to use whatever approach you see fit.

In particular, please provide
1. A working program which takes 揂_tale_of_two_cities.100kwords.obfuscated.txt ?as input and generates an output file where each instance of the word 揳?and 搕he?爄s disambiguated. 
2. The output of this program in two formats
o Plain text format
o Three column TSV with one word per line where column-1 contains original word, column-2 contains obfuscated word, and column-3 contains disambiguated word. Words other than a/the also needs to be present. 
3. An assessment of the output of the program (i.e. the fraction of 揳/the?instances correctly resolved).
4. A description of how you approached the problem, how your program works and how much time you spent.


